coinyep.com 2018-10-21

# Privacy Policy

Last modified: 2018

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, subscribe to email alerts. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Cookies

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

### What are cookies?

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

### How do we use cookies?

A number of our pages use cookies to remember:

  * if you have agreed (or not) to our use of cookies on this site
  * Uses cookies to memorize user settings of the main cryptocurrency and the cryptocurrencies order.

Enabling these cookies is not strictly necessary for the website to work but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. You can delete or block these cookies, but if you do that some features of this site may not work as intended. 

The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally and the pattern data is fully under our control. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here.

### Third party cookies

  * **Google Analytics** \- [Privacy policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/types/) \- [Opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

  *  **Quantcast** \- [Privacy policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/) \- [Opt-out](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out)

  *  **AddThis** \- [Privacy policy](https://www.addthis.com/privacy) \- [Opt-out](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out)

### How to control cookies

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please let us know. [info@coinyep.com](mailto:info@coinyep.com)
